

- Brazil 41745022
- +5571993233375
- ▼ josenascimento16@gmail.com

LINKS:





PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I have experience on a freelance project and that gave me an overview of what is needed to become a complete professional. I'm still looking for my first opportunity as a software developer.

CORE QUALIFICATIONS

- Python, Django, Pytest (unittest)
- HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT
- jQuery, Bootstrap
- GIT, Github, Pythonanywhere
- PostgreSQL, React.js
- Intermediate knowledge on Autolt programmin language
- Willing to learn new technologies

LANGUAGES

Portuguese

English

José Nascimento

Full Stack developer

About Me

As a growing professional software developer (2 years of study and development), i'm always searching for new technologies to improve my skills as a Full Stack developer. I am a calm and detail oriented person and, at the end of the day, what motivates me is the feeling of duty done.

Experience

Autonomous | January 2023 - Current

Freelance

1 year of experience in programming as a freelancer. My most robust project was a web system to generate specific documents that I developed to facilitate communication between schools and the state department. In it I improved my skills in HTML | CSS | JAVASCRIPT | PYTHON | DJANGO | UNITTEST | GIT | BOOTSTRAP | POSTGRESQL | PYTHONANYWHERE (deploy)

Telus International | Jan 2021 - Jan 2023

Internet Consultant

In this period the previous company became Telus International, but I was kept with the same attributions providing data to improve the algorithm of softwares and Al.

Lionbridge | Jan 2015 - Jan 2021

Brazilian rater

Providing information relevant to the use of the internet to improve software of companies like Google and Facebook.

EMBASA | May 2010 - May 2011

Internship

Control and automation - developing Ladder programs for pumping station automation systems.

Power - sizing capacitors, frequency inverters and maintenance on electric motors. Energy efficiency – analyzing the best tariff and contract options for the energy concessionaire, as well as studying and proposing interventions in the equipment of the existing water treatment and pumping stations for better energy efficiency and adequacy with the specific contract.

Education

June - 2011

College of Science and Technology - Área 1, Salvador, BA

Electrical engineer degree | Electronic- Telecommunications

Certifications

Django certification - 2021 Institution: Alura - (99h) **Python certification - 2021** Institution: Alura - (90h)

HTML, CSS, Javascript certification - 2021 Institution: Alura - (110h)

Additional information

- Available to travel and residence change
- Available to a full time job
- Driving license (B) small vehicle